http://www.irishfa.com/privacy

Glentoran Women FC
Crusaders Strikers Women's F.C.
Glentoran Women FC
Crusaders Strikers Women's F.C.
Introduction
1.1. This Privacy Notice explains how the Irish Football Association Group (Irish FA Group) will process the personal information that you provide to us either when using this website or in other communications when we collect personal information from you using this website including via email.
1.2. The Irish FA Group is obligated to comply with General Data Protection Regulations (GDPR).  This Privacy Notice is written to comply with GDPR.  The Irish FA Group takes your privacy seriously and we are committed to processing your personal information in a fair, transparent, and lawful way.
1.3. The Irish FA Group uses Third Parties to help with service delivery and this service delivery may include the use of IrishFA.com.  Specific detail on how this may apply to your data protection is covered in this notice.  Section 4 provides you with information on the Third Parties.
Scope
2.1. This Privacy Notice pertains to the website IrishFA.com.
2.2. This is the IrishFA.com Privacy Notice for the Irish FA Group which consists of the Irish Football Association, the Stadium Development Company, and the Irish FA Foundation.
2.3. This site may contain links to other (third party) sites.  This Privacy Notice does not apply to information collected on third party sites.  The Irish FA Group is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites.
Terms and Definitions
3.1. The Irish FA Group is the owner of the website and you are the user or viewer of the site.
3.2. The Irish FA Group or “us” or “we” or “our” refers to the Irish FA Group.
3.3. The term “you” refers to the user or viewer of the website.
3.4. The term “them” refers to Irish FA Group Third Party affiliates, partners, and/or service providers.
3.5. By using our site or submitting information to us using our site, you are agreeing to the terms of our Privacy Notice.  We will not use and/or disclose your personal information unless it complies with this Privacy Notice.  If you do not agree with this Privacy Notice, you must not use our site or submit information to us through our site.  If you would like to query this Privacy Notice please contact us using the Contact Us link.  Alternatively, you may email us at info@irishfa.com.
IrishFA.com Third Parties
4.1. The Web Bureau deliver the design and build service for the IrishFA.com website.
4.2. Mail Chimp is an application service we use to help us communicate to our customers and fans.
4.3. The Irish FA Group uses Realex Payments for payment services within the IrishFA.com website.
4.4. Ticketmaster is the ticketing service partner for the Irish FA Group.
4.5. Sodexo is the catering service partner for the Stadium Development Company.
4.6. Eventsec is the event security service partner for the Stadium Development Company.
Irish FA Group Marketing
5.1. We would like to send marketing communications to our fans and supporters.  To do this we require your consent.  When we capture your consent to market to you we distinguish between our own marketing activities and marketing on behalf of our third party affiliates, partners, and/or service providers.
5.2 .Our marketing activities include the following:
5.2.1.  Tournaments and matches including at grassroots level, domestic and international football.
5.2.2.  Irish FA Newsletter
5.2.3.  Northern Ireland merchandise
5.2.4.  Educational courses including community initiatives and Coach Education.
5.2.5.  Events including awards ceremonies.
5.2.6.  Football camps
5.2.7.  National Football Stadium at Windsor Park stadium events.
5.3. Our sponsors and partners can be found here https://www.irishfa.com/irish-football-association/sponsors-partners .
Your Information
6.1. We may ask you to provide information to us or collect data from you at points on the site such as:
6.1.1.   Your enquiries or comments to us via our Contact Us link.
6.1.2.   To enter competitions
6.1.3.   To receive download information, newsletters, or other documents
6.1.4.   To purchase goods or services from us
6.1.5.   To register for programmes or events
6.1.6.   To communicate with us for legitimate operational purposes
6.1.7.   To consent to us contacting you for marketing purposes
6.2. The information that you are asked to provide will vary depending on the reason for the data collection.  At the point where we collect your personal information we will provide you with the defined purpose as to why we are collecting it, and how and what we will be using your personal information for.
6.3. The Irish FA Group will keep relevant to the purpose which we require the information and limit the information we request and hold about you.
Processing your personal information
7.1. The Irish FA Group is obligated and committed to processing your information in a lawful way.  At the point where we collect your personal information we will provide you with the defined third party who may have access to your personal information or with whom we may be sharing your personal information with.
7.2. Personal information you submit via IrishFA.com may be shared with Irish FA Group third party affiliates, partners, and/or service providers.  These third parties are not entitled to use your personal information for their own purposes.
7.3. Where you are participating in an Irish FA Group event or competition, we may receive information about you from another team member or official responsible for entering you or your team into our competition.  This will typically involve basic personal information, including your contact email address.
7.4. Where Irish FA Group third party affiliates, partners, and/or service providers would like to directly send you marketing information we will only allow them to do this if you have indicated that you are happy to receive such information from them.
7.5. We may share your information with government, law enforcement agencies, and regulatory bodies if requested as such and when we consider the disclosure of your information to be fair, reasonable, and lawful.
7.6. If you communicate with us through our website we may send you further information that is related to your communication with us.
7.7. If you submit your comments to us via Contact Us we may circulate your comments internally, or with any third party to which the comments pertain, for both training and management purposes.  If you do not want us to do this, please let us know this when you submit your comments.
Protection of Information
8.1. We are committed to protecting your privacy.  We implement various security measures which are both technical and organisational in relation to our processing and sharing of personal information.  However, the nature of the Internet is such that processing or sharing personal information may be done without full security assurance and therefore your personal information could become accessible to unauthorised persons.
8.2. If we believe unauthorised persons have viewed or accessed your personal information, and in doing so impacted your rights to data protection, then we will notify you as soon as is reasonably practicable.  If you believe or feel your personal information has been breached in conjunction with using this site, we ask that you inform us immediately by contacting us using the Contact Us link or by emailing us at info@irishfa.com.
Retention of Your Information
9.1. Personal information you submit to IrishFA.com will be retained for no longer than is necessary to perform the operation for which you have agreed to the submission of the information.  At the point where we collect your personal information we will provide you with the defined period of time reference that we intend to hold the data.
10. Your rights
10.1. You have the right to access the information that the Irish FA Group holds about you.  You may do this by writing to us at info@irishfa.com.  We may require you to verify your identity for us to proceed with your right to access information we may hold about you.  Please note that in certain circumstances the Irish FA Group may withhold access to your information where we have the right to do so under General Data Protection Regulation.
10.2. You have the right to have us delete or erase information that the Irish FA Group holds about you.  You may do this by writing to us at info@irishfa.com.  We may require you to verify your identity for us to proceed with your request.  Please note that in certain circumstances the Irish FA Group may not delete or erase information we hold about you where we have the right to retain the information under General Data Protection Regulation.
10.3. So that we can keep your information up to date and accurate if there is a change to your personal information please let us know the changes via Contact Us or by emailing us at info@irishfa.com.
10.4. If you do not wish to receive any more information from us or be contacted by us in accordance with any of the above, please inform us via Contact Us or by emailing us at info@irishfa.com.
How to contact us
If you have any queries about this Privacy Notice, want the Irish FA Group to stop communicating to you, or want to exercise your rights such as those described above then please contact us via Contact Us or by emailing us at info@irishfa.com.
If you have any questions, queries, or complaints and to exercise your personal data rights, please contact the Data Protection Officer for the Irish FA Group.
Data Protection Authority
The Irish FA Group acknowledges the Information Commissioners Office (ICO) as the authority for data protection in the UK and Northern Ireland.  You may contact the ICO at any time.  Contact details can be found on the website https://ico.org.uk/
Home
International teams
Domestic
Irish FA Foundation
The Irish FA
News
Events
Shop
books
This website uses cookies. Please click Accept and Close to accept the use of cookies on our website. By continuing to browse our website you consent to the use of cookies on this website.
Accept and close
